{
  "sentences": [
    {
      "question": "В Испании (countries)",
      "answer": "In Spain",
      "tasks": ["In"]
    },
    {
      "question": "В Москве (countries)",
      "answer": "In Moscow",
      "tasks": ["In"]
    },
    {
      "question": "На кухне (rooms)",
      "answer": "In the kitchen",
      "tasks": ["In"]
    },
    {
      "question": "В феврале (months)",
      "answer": "In February",
      "tasks": ["In"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Зимой (seasons)",
      "answer": "In winter",
      "tasks": ["In"]
    },
    {
      "question": "В 2018 (years)",
      "answer": "In 2018",
      "tasks": ["In"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Утром (times of day)",
      "answer": "In the morning",
      "tasks": ["In"]
    },
    {
      "question": "В магазине (buildings)",
      "answer": "In the shop",
      "tasks": ["In"]
    },
    {
      "question": "В музее (buildings)",
      "answer": "In the museum",
      "tasks": ["In"]
    },
    {
      "question": "В парке (closed space)",
      "answer": "In the park",
      "tasks": ["In"]
    },
    {
      "question": "В саду (closed space)",
      "answer": "In the garden",
      "tasks": ["In"]
    },
    {
      "question": "На автобусе (transport)",
      "answer": "On the bus",
      "tasks": ["On"]
    },
    {
      "question": "На поезде (transport)",
      "answer": "On the train",
      "tasks": ["On"]
    },
    {
      "question": "1 Марта (days)",
      "answer": "On 1st March",
      "tasks": ["On"]
    },
    {
      "question": "В четверг (days)",
      "answer": "On Thursday",
      "tasks": ["On"]
    },
    {
      "question": "В день святого Валентина (days)",
      "answer": "On Valentine's Day",
      "tasks": ["On"]
    },
    {
      "question": "На полу (surface)",
      "answer": "On the floor",
      "tasks": ["On"]
    },
    {
      "question": "На балконе (surface)",
      "answer": "On the balcony",
      "tasks": ["On"]
    },
    {
      "question": "В школе (places)",
      "answer": "At school",
      "tasks": ["At"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Дома (places)",
      "answer": "At home",
      "tasks": ["At"]
    },
    {
      "question": "В аэропорту (places)",
      "answer": "At the airport",
      "tasks": ["At"]
    },
    {
      "question": "В 6 часов (times)",
      "answer": "At 6 o'clock",
      "tasks": ["At"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Ночью (times)",
      "answer": "At night",
      "tasks": ["At"]
    },
    {
      "question": "В 2:30 (times)",
      "answer": "At half past two",
      "tasks": ["At"]
    },
    {
      "question": "В выходные (times)",
      "answer": "At the weekend",
      "tasks": ["At"]
    },
    {
      "question": "В рождество (festival periods)",
      "answer": "At Christmas",
      "tasks": ["At"]
    }
  ],
  "grammar": {
    "src": "./grammar/in-on-at.webp",
    "layout": "vertical"
  }
}
